{
    "id": "bd314118b99e4d95a8a5c4d737434a15",
    "title": "Agreements And Disagreements",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "93ecd42c8212477584d3182e02e9b2c4",
            "title": "Agreements And Disagreements",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "James doesn’t like cricket. …………………….",
                    "description": "Negative additions to negative remarks are made with nor/neither + auxiliary + subject.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Nor I do",
                        "Nor do I",
                        "So do I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was late for the meeting. ………………………….",
                    "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + subject.",
                    "answers": [
                        "So was he",
                        "So he was",
                        "Nor was he"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She passed the test and …………………………. did I.",
                    "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + subject.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "nor",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have finished my job and …………………………. has he.",
                    "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + subject.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "nor",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susie didn’t arrive. ……………………….. did Mary.",
                    "description": "Negative additions to negative remarks are made with nor/neither + auxiliary + subject.",
                    "answers": [
                        "So",
                        "Neither",
                        "Nor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He didn’t buy it. ……………………………. did I.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Nor",
                        "So",
                        "Neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can play chess ………………………… he can’t.",
                    "description": "Negative additions to affirmative remarks are made with but + subject + auxiliary + n’t.",
                    "answers": [
                        "nor",
                        "and",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She knows how to swim, but ………………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I don't",
                        "don't I",
                        "I know not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My husband doesn’t watch movies …………………………… I do.",
                    "description": "Negative additions to affirmative remarks are made with but + subject + auxiliary + n’t.",
                    "answers": [
                        "but",
                        "and",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She didn’t complain. Neither …………………………… her husband.",
                    "description": "The same auxiliary is used in both statements.",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "does",
                        "has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you ……………………….",
                    "description": "Don't either means the same as neither. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "either",
                        "neither"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is married. ……………………………… her sisters.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "So are",
                        "So is",
                        "Nor are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}